Guide to the Gravity Probe B records SC1274
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Photographs
  - Quadrex, undated (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - probe inside cleanroom, undated (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Doran probe can removal, undated (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - RT sys elect. Breakdown old photo lith, undated (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - delivery probe frans, undated (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Doran delivery probe, undated (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - OKG w/ B scope, undated (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - probe Talyrond Thorwald, undated (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - DoRon Bardas, undated (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - leaky gas pumping system fit ups, 1990 Apr 5 (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - delivery probe frans, undated (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Bardas, undated (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Alkemadde Stanford, undated (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Alkemade, undated (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - cleaning of quartz block, undated (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Alkemade, undated (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Doran and Mike, undated (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Alkemade Stanford Univ., undated (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - 2001 Jul 31, undated (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - photos, 1993 May 3 and 1993 Sep 21 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - equipment, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - presentation photos, undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Queen Air photos, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - 1896, undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Kounan Lee's thesis project, 1992 Spring (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - K. Davis display, 1995 Aug 7 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - outdoor testing slides, undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - GPS field tests, undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Russian guests Gromov- Medvedeu, 1992 Jul (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Freeman D., undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Hansens lab, 1997 Nov 17 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Stu Cobb GPS roof apparatus, 1992 Aug 30 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Trimble circuit boards antenna for reciever, undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Trimble circuit boards antenna for reciever, undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Speedring documents, undated (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Probe/Quartz block, undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - SIA with QB, undated (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - SVA, 1994 Oct 20 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Satelite, undated (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - transparencies, undated (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Equipment photos, undated (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - powerpoint, 2000 Feb (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - GPB, 2003 Apr 18 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - setup pictures, undated (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Removal of air lock after probe insertion, undated (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - machinery photos, undated (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - photos, undated (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - JP Color Laboratory price list, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - JP Color Laboratory price list, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - photo labs and services, undated (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Keeble, undated (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - JP color labs, undated (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - black and white photo, undated (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - X-mas photos, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - X-mas photos, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - random pics, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - outer space slides, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Su Wen Wang, 1992 Sep 25 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Hansen labs 12/13, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - viewgraphs, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - celebation pictures, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - STU folks, 1993 Jan (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Halloween party, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Staff pics, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Jackie, the probe, the owl, Andy Jack, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - GPB personell/ beige background misc photos, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Equipment photos, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Equipment photos, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Equipment photos, undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Enrique Berberian Lawrence, David S. Cruz, 1995 Apr (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - baby pictures, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - lab work photos, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - hansen labs, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Christmas, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Dale Rosemary Gill photos, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - lab photos, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - lab photos, undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - lab photos, undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Jackie, the probe, the owl, Andy Jack, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - GPB personnel (beige background misc), 1989 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Enrique Berberian Lawrence, David S. Cruz, 1995 Apr (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Damaged quartz, 1996 Nov 15 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Hansen labs people, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Novah, Powell, Gazit, Evans Walter O'Conner, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Linda, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - readout test A probe, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - slide, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - presentation, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - demonstration slides, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - equipment, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - person, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - coiling, fan, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - equipment pieces, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - program review, 2002 Jun 19 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - machinery, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - testing, machinery, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Shake test fix caging, undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Shake test fix caging, undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Frans hi speed spin sasha probe horiz., undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - misc., undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - review, 1991 Nov (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Sasha xtra's housings, 1991 Oct (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Daron/John caging mech test Amy, 1991 Octoer 25 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Barry xtras, 1991 Oct 28 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - misc duplicates, undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Baron Storey, undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - tubes, equipment, undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - testing, 1990 Jun (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Linda, undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - equipment, undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Fairbank, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Jed Ale, 1997 Nov (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Int. potluck, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Sasha Buchman, undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - potluck, undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Raffi, Wanda, Trimble circuit boards antenna for reciever, 1992 Nov 7 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Christmas, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Pullen, Hiro, Mae, Compact squid, Cobb- Clark, 1992 May (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Fightruy, Walter, Awele, 1992 Oct 9 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Freeman D., undated (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Emily, Jim, Dean, Grey, Linda, GPS recievers, 1992 Nov 10 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Denise, Alex, undated (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - photo album Stanford University Gyro Relativity Experiment, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - binder of slides, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - photo album, 1988 Mar 25 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - photo album, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - vufoil notebook book 1, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Duhamel Thesis, 1984 Apr (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Telescope photos, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Probe integ. Series #2 negatives, 1997 May (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Probe integ. Series #2 photos, 1997 May (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - probe integ. Series A (#1), 1997 May (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Probe QB integration, 1994 Oct 8 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Studio reflex- PAO product reprints, 2004 Aug (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Vandenberg AFB, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Gyro housing 2nd - 3rd drawer, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - equipment parts photos, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Gyro slide, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - equipment pieces photos, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - P. Gyro w. Helmholtz, 1988 Jul (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Gyro Bracket, 1995 Jun 28 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Caging parts, 1991 Apr (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Caging (exploded), 1991 Mar (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Low temp, high speed gyro test pictures, undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Probe for single gyro test, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Low temp gyro test commissioning probe, undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Voltage amp. For low temp. GSV, 1993 Nov (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Low temperature fast spin speed test system. And its designer TED ALE, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Quartz block photo, 1990 Jun (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Quartz block, 1990 Jun (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - QBA failure analysis, 1993 Jul (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Quartz blank, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - GP-B IRT-I photos gang sheet unused negatives, 1988 May 24 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - IRT 1 Birdcage (full), 1988 Jul (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - IRT 1 Birdcage, 1988 Jul (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - IRT 1 - full view, 1988 Jul (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - IRT - Birdcage bolt (close up), 1988 Jul (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - IRT- birdcage - bolt - Engar, 1988 Jul (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - PQB - lifted from clamp, 1988 Jul (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Support struct. Lowered to block, 1988 Jul (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - PQB - clamp (open), 1988 Jul (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - PQB - VISE - hand, 1988 Jul (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - QB support struct and bolt, 1988 Jul (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - putting together photo, undated (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - quartz photos, undated (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - QB and shield, 1988 Jul (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - quartz photos, undated (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - quartz photos, undated (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - PQB - prec mnpltr hand, 1988 Jul (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Quartz block bolts, undated (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - quartz photo, undated (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Quartz block, undated (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Sasha's doc, undated (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Sasha's papers, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - notes- seminar, undated (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Francis seminar, undated (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Sasha's PP files, undated (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Gyro measurement during integration, 1990 Apr (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - gyro integration, 1990 Apr (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Gyro integ setup for fist, 1990 Apr (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Qtz. Block handling prior to gyro integ 1990 Apr (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Cleaning the quartz blockprior to gyro integ., 1990 Apr (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Squid - Energy Spectral Density readout and shielding, undated (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - equipment parts photos, undated (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - misc. housings, undated (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Housing, 1991 Dec (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Housing halves (joined), undated (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - housing readout cable (mock-up - detachable stripline), 1991 Dec (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - housings featuring lands, 1991 Nov (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Dummy housings - uncoated coated with Niobum in holding fixture, undated (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - Single dummy housing half Doron, 1987 Mar (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - Housing spin up, undated (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - Housing half and ruler, Paul Bayer, undated (Box 26, Folder 66)
  - Housing - no gyro, 1988 Jul (Box 26, Folder 67)
  - unlabeled negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 68)
  - Gyroscope housing half with UV charge control fiber optics assembly, undated (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - Optical read- out hardware version 1, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 70)
  - Optical read- out hardware mounted in gyroscope housing Version 1, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 71)
  - Fiber optic connection in gyroscope housing, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 72)
  - Read- out half of gyroscope housing with bonded read-out cable, undated (Box 26, Folder 73)
  - read out gyroscope housing half with electrodes, pick up loop, and read out loops, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 74)
  - Gyro integ (enlargements), 1994 Nov 18 (Box 26, Folder 75)
  - Gyro integration, 1994 Nov 18 (Box 26, Folder 76)
  - SIA/ probe integ., undated (Box 26, Folder 77)
  - installing SQUID/ spider assembly onto birdcage, undated (Box 26, Folder 78)
  - Best of …. Photos, undated (Box 26, Folder 79)
  - telescope detector, 1998 Jan-Feb (Box 26, Folder 80)
  - Story of fist B. Storey, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 81)
  - Machining the quartz B. Storey, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 82)
  - Einstein's offspring B. Storey, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 83)
  - GP-B B. Storey, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 84)
  - Spin- off's B. Storey, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 85)
  - GP-B management experiment B. Storey, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 86)
  - Schiff, Leonard B. Storey, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 87)
  - Milliarc Second B. Storey, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 88)
  - Black holes B. Storey, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 89)
  - Quartz block B. Storey, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 90)
  - GPB gyro photos, undated (Box 26, Folder 91)
  - equipment slides, undated (Box 26, Folder 92)
  - Andy/STU/ Doron's back, watching probe, undated (Box 26, Folder 93)
  - probe int #3 negatives, 1997 May (Box 26, Folder 94)
  - probe int #3 photos, undated (Box 26, Folder 95)
  - Probe photos, 1994 Nov 16 (Box 26, Folder 96)
  - Stu, SIA photos, undated (Box 26, Folder 97)
  - Tilting the QB, 1994 Dec 3 (Box 26, Folder 98)
  - Doron Kneeling photos, undated (Box 26, Folder 99)
  - Efraim SIA, undated (Box 26, Folder 100)
  - SIA on cart moving under probe photos, undated (Box 26, Folder 101)
  - View of probe inside airlock in preparation for final FIRST integration, 1990 Jun (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Artificial star located in fist operations room, undated (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - DEWAR pump (front), undated (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Buchman Data Acquisition - suspension system and Dewar, undated (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - C. Warren operation a Valve on Gas Manifold console spin-up system, undated (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Dewar-pump Warren Malekian, undated (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Andy Probe, undated (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Andy/ Stu/ Doron Probe SIA, undated (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Need to ID, undated (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Muhlfelder Squid Signals on Oscilloscope Squid Electronics Rack, undated (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Dewar and Pumping Station, 1990 Jul (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Fist operations set-up, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Transparencies, undated (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Einstein artwork, 2001 Jun 18 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Artwork photos, undated (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Early gyro spinup, undated (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - equipment photos, undated (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Top hat of IRT probe visible above top of edd, 1991 Aug (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Dale Geel photo, undated (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Hansens lab, 1997 Nov 17 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Hansens lab, 1997 Nov 17 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Sasha negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Jon Salmon, Darell Charleston, AC negatives, 1997 Nov 17 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Hansens lab negatives, 1997 Nov 17 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - room photos not good GPS guys negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Thorwald- Lapping Melrology, undated (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - hansens lab, 1997 Nov 17 (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Xmas Freeman, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - Farewell reception program, 2004 Nov 5 (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - loose photos, undated (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - Juan Ceva, Kounan Lee negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - Jed, Ale, 1997 Nov 17 (Box 28, Folder 59)
  - Mike McGeruin, 1997 Nov 17 (Box 28, Folder 60)
  - Yusuf, Carolyn, 1992 Aug 28 (Box 28, Folder 61)
  - Yusuf, Carolyn, 1992 Aug 28 (Box 28, Folder 62)
  - Hansens Lab, Russ Hacker, 1997 Nov 17 (Box 28, Folder 63)
  - Kasdin Wiktor negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 64)
  - Gutt, Yon, Sines (lab), 1992 May 22 (Box 28, Folder 65)
  - Gutt, Yon, Sines (lab), 1992 May 22 (Box 28, Folder 66)
  - Hansen lab, Clark open house Maria, undated (Box 28, Folder 67)
  - Jeff Wade, Paulo Carini, Filly Reeder, Mary Wood, Alex Febbery, Altzman Coon, 1992 Oct 28 (Box 28, Folder 68)
  - Rheinhard photo, Teaque project, John Mester, 1992 Aug 13 (Box 28, Folder 69)
  - Langenstein Richet Zhou Buchman Muhlfelder Pullen van Ho, undated (Box 28, Folder 70)
  - Stu prototype, 1991 Aug (Box 28, Folder 78)
  - photoshoot, 1991 Aug 1-2 (Box 28, Folder 79)
  - Magnetic coils flank the integrated FIST instrument during testing, 1990 Jun (Box 28, Folder 80)
  - Lowering airlock onto EDD during FIST integration, 1990 Jun (Box 28, Folder 81)
  - Dewar (wrapped) vertical taber, 1990 Jul (Box 28, Folder 82)
  - Dewar, Doron mike with (wrapped), 1990 Jul (Box 28, Folder 83)
  - EDD airlock, 1991 Aug (Box 28, Folder 84)
  - Hansen's lab, 1997 Nov 17 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Stu folks, 1993 Jan (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Halloween party, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - unlabeled negatives, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Gerda's Birthday telescope room, 1992 Oct 27 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Public Relations
  - Gravity Probe B Fact sheets, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Satellite Test of the Equivalence Priniple (STEP) - Stanford University in response to SMEX, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases on GRAVITY PROBE-B (C. W. Francis Everitt) and Articles on Scientific Interests, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - GP-B Testing Einstein's Universe #1 (white binder), undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - GP-B Testing Einstein's Universe #2 (blue binder), undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - GP-B Testing Einstein's Universe #3 (white binder with picture-only cover), undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - NASA Press Kit, 1992 Jun (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Astronomy Magazine, 2002 Jan (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - dSpace news magazine, 2002 Jan (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Physical Review paper by Lange, 1998 May 18 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Inside the Santa Ynez Valley, 2003-2004 Winter (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Campus report newspaper, 1990 Feb 7 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Nature magazine, 2003 Nov 27 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - popular science magazine, 2003 Nov (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - ingenia magazine, 2003 Jul-Aug (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Scientific, 2003 Spring (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Gravity Probe B info card, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Aerospace American magazine, 2003 Jul (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Nature magazine, 2002 Apr 11 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Crosslink magazine, 2002 summer (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Engineering and Science magazine, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Stanford magazine, 2004 Jul-Aug (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Stanford magazine, 2004 Jan-Feb (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Stanford magazine, 2004 Mar-Apr (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Discover magazine, 2002 Jul (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Science news magazine, 2004 Sep 25 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - GEO magazine, 2005 Feb 2 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Cold Facts news, 2008 Fall (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - GP-B launch companion, undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - NASA Marshall Star, 2005 Oct 13 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - GP-B spacetime info, undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - NASA relativity mission pamphlet, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - NASA GP-B info cards, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Natural History magazine, 2005 Mar (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Stanford magazine, 2009 Jul-Aug (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Gravity Probe B educator's guide, 2004 Oct (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Gravity Probe fact folder, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - NASA images, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Gravity Probe B educator's guide, 2004 Oct (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - space poster, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Relativity Mission NASA stickers, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - space poster, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - space poster, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Probe B program Info package, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Gravity Probe B folder, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Gravity Probe B facts, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Space poster, Einstein, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - space time poster, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - proposal poster Gravity Probe B, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - GE proposal cover, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Fairchild proposal cover, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Lockheed images, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - SPIE originals, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - NASA final report, 2008 Dec (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Post-flight analysis final report, 2007 Mar (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - GP-B brochure info, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - time delay corrections, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - 3D position error, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - RAIM availability, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - LAAS lab, DGPS coverage of Europe, undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - The Gravity Probe by Taubes DISCOVER, 1997 Mar (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Music of the Spheres by Lannotta, NEW SCIENTIST, 1996 Aug 31 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Putting Einstein to the Test- in Space, Research News, 1991 Nov (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - The Einstein Test by Kuznik, Air Space, 1993 Dec/Jan (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Gravity Probe B to Test Einstein's work, Stanford Daily, 2000 Apr 10 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Ashby, Relativity and Global Positioning System, Physics Today, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Discover magazine, 1997 Mar (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Manufacturing Engineering magazine, 1983 Apr (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Stanford Report newspaper, 2005 Oct 12 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Popular Science reprint NASA/Stanford article, 1983 Aug (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Boeing folder, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Sasha/GPB talk ppt, 2001 Oct (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - proposal, 2004 Oct 29 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - K. Sun proposal, 2004 Oct 17 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Ke-Xun proposal, 2004 Oct (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Sasha/ weekly meetings, undated (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - List mtg/ SLAC, undated (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Executive summary space security, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Science reprint article Larson, Bodin, Gomberg, 2003 May 30 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - article SICE, undated (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - SAPS BUCHMAN publications, undated (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Credibility of GPB Storyboard/Parkinson/DeBra, 2002 Feb 8 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - articles, 2001, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Gravity Probe B educator's guide, 2004 Oct (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - AA 272C custom course material, 1995 spring (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - GPS software review, 1999 Oct 18 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - TANS VECTOR, undated (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - GPS thermal vac test procedure PO-470, 1999 Jun 20 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Proposal for XNAV, 2004 ctober 22 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Gravity probe b articles, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Gravity Probe B: a Management Study, 2006 Apr 21 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Post flight analysis-- interim report, 2004 Oct (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Gyro Suspension Unit Preliminary design review, 1995 Dec 18 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Proposal, 1993 May 28 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Gravity Probe B Articles, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - GP-B Post-Flight Analysis, 2007 Mar (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Gravity Probe B Relativity Mission Flight Software design specification, 1998 Jun 14 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Gravity Probe B Relativity Mission Flight Software design specification, 1998 Jun 14 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Gravity Probe B Relativity Mission Flight Software design specification, 1998 Jun 14 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - The GP-B Green Book, 1980 Jun (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - GPB news clippings, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - the GP-B Dossier, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - HEPL annual report, 2008 Apr 2 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - HEPL research updates, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - history of HEPL, 2007 Nov 5 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - empty folder, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - blank folder, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Bob Kahn GP-B notes, 2004 Aug (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - brochure, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Bob Kahn Gp-B notes messages, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Kahn Laboratory notebook, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Gravity Probe B Experiment press kit, 2004 Apr (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Launch Companion, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - NASA final report, 2008 Dec (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Gravity Probe B folder, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Gravity Probe B folder, undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Gravity Probe B folder, undated (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Gravity Probe B folder, undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Gravity Probe B folder, undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Gravity Probe B folder, undated (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Gravity Probe B folder, undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Gravity Probe B folder, undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Gravity Probe B folder, undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Simulation information, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)